class DataBase {
  static List<Map<String, dynamic>> quizData = [
    {
      "question": " Kerala is ________ largest state by population?",
      "options": ["Tenth","Eleventh","Thirteenth","Seventeenth"],
      "answer": 2,
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the capital of india?",
      "options": ["Kerala", "Goa", "Delhi", "Kolkata"],
      "answer": 2,
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the national animal of india?",
      "options": ["Lion", "Tiger", "Bear", "None of The Above"],
      "answer": 1,
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the Missile Man of india?",
      "options": [" Nehru", " Gandhi", " Abdul kalam", "Vikram Sarabai"],
      "answer": 2,
    },
    {
      "question":
          " When is republic celebrated in india?",
      "options": [
        "May 1st",
        "August 15th",
        "October 2nd",
        "January 26th"
      ],
      "answer": 3,
    },
    {
      "question":
          " Technopark, the largest Information Technology park in Asia in terms of area, is situated in _________?",
      "options": [" Palakkad", "Trivandrum", "Cochin"," Malappuram"],
      "answer": 1,
    },
    {
      "question": " _______ is the first airport in India developed under a public-private partnership (PPP) model?",
      "options": [
        "Cochin International Airport", "Calicut International Airport", "Trivandrum International"," Airport None of the above" ],
      "answer": 0,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Digestion of food in human beings begins in which part of the alimentary canal?",
      "options": ["Liver", "Kidney", "Mouth", "Large intestine"],
      "answer": 2,
    },
    {
      "question":
          " Which of the following is responsible for nitrogen fixation?",
      "options": ["Fungus", "Bacteria", "Virus", "Insects"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Which of the given industries uses limestone as a raw material?",
      "options": ["Paper", "Cement", "Textile", "Leather"],
      "answer": 1,
    },
  ];
}
